[
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_1",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "advice",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_2",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "last but not least",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "h"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_3",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "to be tempted",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_4",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "anxious",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_5",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "plenty",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_6",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "repetition",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_7",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a stroll around the block",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "f"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_8",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "to cover something up",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "nervous and worried",
      "b": "to be strongly attracted to doing something",
      "c": "a good or full amount",
      "d": "the act of doing something again",
      "e": "an opinion or recommendation about what someone should do",
      "f": "a short walk around your local area",
      "g": "to put something over something so that you can't see it",
      "h": "an expression used before the last thing in a list, to say that it is equally as important"
    },
    "answer": "g"
  },

  {
    "id": "b2_lis_9",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher wants the students to …",
    "options": [
      "a. take notes after she has finished speaking.",
      "b. take notes while she is speaking.",
      "c. forget about taking notes."
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_10",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher suggests eating …",
    "options": [
      "a. sugary snacks.",
      "b. only apples.",
      "c. fruit and cereals."
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_11",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher suggests finding a study place with a lot of …",
    "options": [
      "a. light.",
      "b. space.",
      "c. books."
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_12",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "If students feel stressed they should …",
    "options": [
      "a. go to bed.",
      "b. go out for a walk.",
      "c. drink some water."
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_13",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "Students are advised to …",
    "options": [
      "a. select the important things to learn.",
      "b. read through everything once.",
      "c. make notes about every topic."
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_14",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher understands that repeating things can be …",
    "options": [
      "a. difficult.",
      "b. uninteresting.",
      "c. tiring."
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_15",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "Students can do past exam papers …",
    "options": [
      "a. in the library only.",
      "b. at home if they take photocopies.",
      "c. in the after-school study group."
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_16",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher recommends a break of five minutes every …",
    "options": [
      "a. hour.",
      "b. two hours.",
      "c. thirty minutes."
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_17",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "It's important to …",
    "options": [
      "a. eat regularly.",
      "b. sleep when you feel tired.",
      "c. keep hydrated."
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "b2_lis_18",
    "level": "B2",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "question": "The teacher is sure that the students will …",
    "options": [
      "a. pass their exams.",
      "b. fail their exams.",
      "c. do their best."
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  }
]
